<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Basic</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="article_text"> <b>HOW TO USE?</b> \n\n <b>Cara Menyambungkan :</b> \n\n 1. Aktifkan koneksi Bluetooth Handphone Anda. Pastikan visible atau terlihat semua perangkat. \n\n 2. Cari koneksi dengan nama REVOLT atau koneksi tanpa nama(hanya kode), kemudian sambungkan dengan password default “1234”. \n\n 3. Buka aplikasi REVOLT.ID (Advance), klik tombol Bluetooth dan kemudian pilih nama Bluetooth REVOLT. \n\n 4. Masukkan password default “revolt”. \n\n\n <b>Ganti Password :</b> \n\n 1. Silahkan pilih menu, pilih CHANGE PASSWORD. \n\n 2. Masukkan password terbaru. Penggantian password dapat dilakukan apabila device sudah tersambung. \n\n 3. Minimal password adalah 5 karakter dan maksimal 10 karakter. Password dapat menggunakan kombinasi angka, huruf dan simbol. \n\n\n <b>Perhatian!</b> \n\n 1. Apabila koneksi tidak tersambung maka disarankan untuk menutup aplikasi terlebih dahulu dan kemudian coba kembali. \n\n 2. Jika masih terjadi error silahkan matikan module dan kemudian hidupkan kembali. \n\n\n <b>How to Connect :</b> \n\n 1. Activate your Bluetooth Mobile connection. Make sure visible to all devices. \n\n 2. Locate the connection with the name REVOLT or without name(just code), then connect it with default password 1234.\n\n 3. Open REVOLT.ID app (Advance), click Bluetooth button and then select Bluetooth REVOLT. \n\n 4. Enter the default password revolt. \n\n\n <b>Change Password :</b> \n\n 1. Please select menu, choose CHANGE PASSWORD. \n\n 2. Enter the latest password. Changing passwords can be done when the device is connected. \n\n 3. Minimum password is 5 characters and maximum 10 characters. Password can be use a combination of numbers, letters and symbols. \n\n\n <b>Attention!</b> \n\n 1. If connection is not connected then it is advisable to close the application first and then try again. \n\n 2. If error still occur please turn off module and turn on again. \n\n </string>
    <string name="about"> Revolt.id is build precisely and accurately to meet the demand of modern system and satisfaction of airsuspension technology. \n\n Minimal OS : Jelly bean \n\n Version : 2.0.1 \n\n Website : www.revolt.id</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
</resources>
